Okay, let's get started.
Good evening, everyone. I'm Sherry, the designer of Lines of Marvelous.
Today, I'm going to explain to you guys
the process of making this Christmas suit
that is included in these promotions.
First of all, I will show you
the basic shirt pattern
as a background picture.
Then I will change its proportion
and let it match our model.
Then when changing the proportion,
I will mainly refer to the shoulder line of this model.
That is to say, if this set of clothes
is a normal size,
then basically this shoulder line
is parallel to the shoulder line of this model.
Today's live broadcast will have a screen recording.
Today's live broadcast will have a screen recording,
but it will be released a little later.
Don't post the screen recording in private, everyone. Thank you.
Then here I will change its size.
Then after slightly matching its shoulder line,
I will draw this line along this reference picture.
Then this reference picture,
you can actually search it online.
You can basically find it on the clothing board.
Let's be quick here.
After jumping through these
very long time to make this board,
we will first import a set of already drawn boards.
How to add it?
Are you talking about that picture?
That picture, you can just use the background picture to add it.
Then here I will first
arrange these boards in this 3D environment.
The key to arranging is to try not to let them
be too far from the model.
Then paste it near the model.
Just arrange them well.
Then next is sewing.
This part I actually
speeded up in the video.
Because these are all very simple.
Just some simple sewing process.
Then after I finished sewing it in advance,
I put it on the model.
The shoulder line.
This is a video,
not real.
This video is about twice the quality.
The shoulder line refers to this line.
When we add the background, this line, for example, you take this line and align it with the center line of our model,
the shoulder will be in this position.
Just look at this point and the shoulder of the model.
Because for example, this point is closer to the model.
For example, you put this board here.
It's a lot bigger than the model's shoulder.
Then when it's worn on the body, it must be too big.
And then because the shoulder line is a point that is easier to align.
You go to the waist or something.
These are all easy to change.
The shoulder here actually affects the whole set of clothes.
So we usually refer to the shoulder or the waist as reference.
In fact, modern fashion is good.
In my previous video,
I wanted to do a cultural restoration.
There is a reference on our油管.
Some tutorials on making this kind of medieval clothing.
You can go and have a look.
But we also have some plans now.
That is, in the next year's live broadcast,
we may do some more complex styles of dresses in the medieval period of cultural restoration.
Dabrit.
I don't know what that is.
Then let's continue first.
Then I was thinking about what this dress looks like.
Then I went online to look at some reference pictures.
I found that their neck seems to be quite large.
Then I will draw some lines on the clothes with a 3D drawing tool.
Then after converting them to internal patterns,
look at its position and then cut it off.
Of course, you can also cut it directly.
I just want to refer to that position a little bit.
Then I will delete the excess of these panels.
Then I will take a look at what position this dress is in.
In fact, when I first made these clothes,
I didn't think about what it should look like.
I usually sit down and think about what kind of dress I want to make.
Then, for example, I thought about it.
It seems that this kind of dress goes together with the front.
It doesn't have that buckle.
Then I just deleted that door.
It's the door to the original shirt.
Live broadcast for about half an hour.
The main content is almost the same.
This part is about half an hour.
It's over in three hours.
Then there will be some reviews of the overall live broadcast this year.
When it comes to this,
I found that this model's clothes,
you can see its size.
It's still a little different from our model itself.
For example, its sleeves are very big here.
Then I just wanted to say that I wanted to change it.
Change this dress.
Change this dress dress a little bit.
It's a little bit deeper.
Then my first step is that I will reverse activate this sleeve version.
Let the clothes alone like a horse clip.
Activate in the 3D environment.
Go check it out.
Check out its wearing effect.
It's a little big.
I also think this model is pretty big.
Then I'll take a look at the transparent one.
I found it a little bit wide.
So I'm going to adjust it horizontally.
But if you pull it directly,
The curve of the sleeve here,
That's the curve of my mouse here.
It's going to change along with it.
So I added a straight line here.
In this way,
I can make sure that this curve line
When I adjust it here,
It won't follow along.
That is to say,
I will fix this curve line.
Because I think it's here.
The curve line seems to be not very different.
It's down here.
Anyway, there are some differences.
Oh,
And then after I'm done,
I'll turn on the transparent display.
And then I'm going to compare
The way we're wearing this dress.
And the model's body shape.
Then you can see that
Because we're on this board right now.
It's vertical on the side.
And then put it on the model.
Then this side is straight on the left.
The right side is straight.
He must be like a straight bucket.
But our Hana,
His figure must be more.
Out of shape.
Yes.
So he's on his waist.
His amount must be
It's going to be more tight.
And then the chest side.
He might have more fabric.
So I just wanted to say,
Change this dress a little bit.
Take a look at the model.
Oh,
Yeah.
And then I'm going to put it here.
Create a straight line.
And then I'm going to put it in there.
Make some adjustments.
For example,
If I make 20 in front of me,
I'm going to make 20 in the back.
And then I'm looking at it.
Oh,
His size seems to be a little bit.
Not enough.
I'm going to go in there a little bit more.
And then there's another one.
Why do I pull these two points down here?
It's because I found out that I used to wear this position.
It's the thinnest position of the waist.
And the thinnest position of Hana's waist.
There's no match.
That's a relatively close-fitting dress.
His thinnest point.
It should be right.
So I'm going to pull this point down a little bit.
And then after changing these points,
I'm going to change them to a curve point.
Because there's a good thing about changing to a curve point.
Generally speaking,
There's a curve on the side of this dress.
It's not just a straight line.
If you add a straight line,
It's going to be like the vermilion just now.
He's going to have some protruding feet.
He doesn't look like a curve.
The curve is a very smooth transition.
Because it's a curve now.
You can see it here.
It can be attached to the human body curve.
If it's a straight line,
It looks like it's going to be very hard.
That's a couple.
Clothes like a couple.
His curve must be more beautiful.
And then I add two straight lines.
Because I want to say.
You can see the curve of this dress.
It's normal here.
But there are some protruding feet on the bottom.
So I just wanted to say.
So I'm going to adjust the bottom of these boards.
And then let this.
The bottom of the dress.
He won't have two protruding shoulders.
And then when you're changing the curve on the side of this dress.
Be sure to pay attention.
Try to make this corner on your side.
That's the corner at the bottom.
The corner where the other boards are sewn together.
It's a straight corner.
Only when it's a straight corner.
You sew them together on both sides.
That's why he won't have the protruding foot.
You see, I'm trying my best here.
I'm going to adjust it to a straight corner.
And then by adding some curve points.
And then let's make our whole set of clothes.
His curve on the side is a little bit rounder.
After adjustment, simulate it.
You can see.
His shoulders won't be as prominent as they were just now.
And then what?
I'm in.
I'm going to check the sleeves again.
You can see the sleeves here.
For example, it's like this now.
The sleeves here.
He's going to have a protruding shoulder.
Then you want to imagine it.
Now we haven't sewn the sleeves up yet.
If we sew the sleeves up.
Does he have a point here?
Pull the sleeves up.
That's going to form some ugly wrinkles.
So what we're going to do now is.
I'm going to finish this sleeve here.
And then there's a flat side here.
After adjustment.
We're going to go slowly.
Make some adjustments to his side.
Including I'm going to choose to add some straight lines.
And then pull him back a little bit.
It's actually a little bit of a change.
Let's make this point.
It's going to be a straight corner here, too.
It's going to be a straight corner on both sides.
It's going to be a smooth line.
After I'm done.
I'm going to start the simulation.
After the simulation.
Although the sleeves are flat here.
But you can see the chest here.
There's still one more piece.
That's the point I'm pointing at right now.
I'm going to give him a straight line here.
That's where I'm going to give him a straight line.
And then I'm going to add it.
By forming a gap here.
And then sew this gap up.
After that.
You can make this curve fit our model better.
That's what we're going to save.
One of the functions.
You can see.
I'm just testing it all the time.
I'm going to open this.
How big do I want to open it?
To make this.
The clothing is more suitable.
Hana.
And then after I've adjusted it.
I think this sleeve seems to be a little bit.
This gap is too big.
So I'm going to keep adjusting it.
I want this sleeve to be able to.
Don't be that big.
In fact, it's just this side.
This curve.
Pulling up more and more.
And then once I see.
The amount here has changed a lot.
I'm going to make this here.
Dig this gap.
A little bit bigger.
In fact, it's just a step.
To make this sleeve smaller.
And then let him stick to it.
Our model's curve.
In fact, this section.
Although it looks a little bit boring.
But this section is indeed.
A little bit.
It's a little bit.
But we're still.
Bizzy.
Look at the building for me.
My body of medallion.
Oh my god.
In fact, where is youraser?
Yeah.
Here.
Probably.
Exactly where I am.
Okay, this one.
I have a little bit.
I haven't even gotten up yet.
This one not.
It's right.
We'll just.
He's looking for.
His hair iron.
Yes.
That.
No Movement.
Of course.
And then.
Hey, I need to grab this hair iron.
Yeah.
There they go.
Oh yeah.
Here we go.
Okay.
the length of the shirt is not the right one
so I might have to
modify the length of the sleeve
when I modify the length of the sleeve
I will choose
the tool called change length
because it can maintain
the original curve
and here I actually tried it a few times
I found that it seems to be
just adjusted
and will be changed
so I don't care
just change the length
as long as the curve is ok
and after changing it
you can see that it becomes a more close-fitting shirt
and there are no extra wrinkles
after that I will use the
fill-out extension
to make this shirt
from a normal top
to a
slightly longer
skirt
actually the skirt is still a short skirt
after changing it
I feel that the waist
is still not thin enough
it's not the kind of effect I want
so I added some points
and then changed the seam line
because I have to adjust
the point later
I hope to keep the waist
as thin as possible
the front and the back can match
I am still
fixing the pattern
after finishing the pattern
I will move it to the side
and then make this
pattern
into a bigger
so that the skirt
will look like a dress
and its
skirt will
because of the weight
it will fall down
it will look like a dress
the chats are so quiet
are you all
studying seriously?
no one is interacting with you
if you have any questions
you can ask in the chat
then I will change the bottom
to a curve
because as you can see
when the bottom is straight
it won't be flat
like now
you have to change the bottom
to a curve
add a curve
and put it on the body
then it will be flat
like this
you are all so serious
then I will
add a curve
to the inside of the dress
then add a belt
for the belt pattern
you have to add layers
so that it can be worn faster
after adding layers
I will
merge it in the front
I found that
this video is a bit too fast
because when I was doing it myself, my hands were fast too
so fast
and then I put the
curve out
let me see if I can
speed up the video
oh, I can speed up the video
let's speed up
then I added a belt
because as you can see
after we put the curve
open
the fabric here
is actually piled up
and then
I hope that the curve of the waist
is ok
but I also hope that the fold here
becomes less
so I choose to add a
curve here
using this tool
the waist curve tool
add a curve here
how to use
the handle
is
I will talk about it later
this tool
MD
is very smooth
I think
this is related to your hardware
when I was operating
it was not very good
then
I will put this sewing line
and then open the simulation
you can see that
the spine of the waist becomes less
then I will adjust
the position of the waist
this is because the fabric here
becomes less
so the fold becomes less
then the reason why I add this belt
is because I want to hide this
bottom part of the rope
into the belt
so that I won't find
a rope here
because as you can see
if you add a rope
sometimes there will be this protruding place
because you sew up
these two sides
naturally there will be some fabric here
so that the fabric can be even
so that we will use the tool
to pull the fabric
then I will
adjust the rope little by little
to see the position of the rope
actually I mainly want to hide
the rope into the belt
so that it can't be seen
I didn't expect that
actually I am lazy
otherwise the board of the clothes
will be changed
I will add some ropes
then I will use the tool
to pull the fabric
pull the fabric
use the negative value
to pull the fabric
as you can see
the fabric here becomes less
it is actually like
a shrink to the grid
when I add
oops, too fast
when I add the rope
this point here
will slowly become flat
will be the center
this grid will become smaller
this is the function of the ruler
the ruler
in addition to its negative value
it can smooth out
these folds
if you use the positive value
to shrink the value of the ruler
into the positive value
it will be a tool
to have more fabric
for that
so that you can have more
or less folds
on the clothes
yes, it is
quite smooth
you can understand it this way
then I will
draw a collar
oh
yes, I remember
this clothes doesn't have a collar
I drew a shawl
my shawl is based on my brain
I feel that the shawl
should look like this
then the inside of the shawl
is re-enacted by me
just draw it
actually, now
you can see that this fold
is almost the same as the fold
I usually make clothes
so I make clothes quite fast
then turn the water bottle
and arrange it to the back
actually, the grid
has changed a lot
no, actually the grid
hasn't changed
the unit
the grid in the area you chose
has become bigger
sometimes
at the end of the process
the UV arrangement
the size of some panels
will be different from 2D
you can see in the UV editor
there is a
re-arrange
UV
to 2D panel
this function
is the same
then after I finished
sewing this shawl
I found that this shawl
seems to be smaller
then it is still a little bit
for example, I think it is in the back
you see there is a gap in the back
I will probably
change this shawl
along the back
is there any material
no
this is not
for everyone
if you want this panel
I can send it to you
but this project file
can't send it to you
then when the shawl
sit here
you can see
actually this shawl
has some problems
there is a playback
there will be a playback
then
this shawl
you can take a look
it is a shawl
the shawl we usually imagine
it is attached to the human body
then I
because this shawl
is a curve I drew by myself
you can see
the curve here
after wearing on our model
it will have two
these two protruding
for those who look at us
it looks like the model's shoulder
is protruding
so when we see
this kind of
inappropriate curve on our clothes
we will fix it
on the 2D panel
this part
really
does it look good
I think the flat one looks better
then I will fix it
maybe this is the compulsion
I was looking at it
I was thinking about the reason
why this shawl
will have problems
then I thought about it
it seems to be the curve
so I fixed it
I used the editor tool
to fix the curve
make it a little flat
don't make it so crooked
then it will fit the model's curve
for the fabric value setting
I will show you
the video
with the physical attribute setting
in that video
you can probably understand
then this one
also has the physical attribute setting
but I'm not sure
if I recorded it
seems like I didn't record
a lot of things related to that
then I will
freeze the panel
because in the original
it was like this
so now
we are going to
put the shawl outside
after putting it outside
what am I doing
I think the shawl
is a little short
and it looks a little weird
then I was thinking
should the shawl be
longer
otherwise it feels like
there is nothing on it
then I was thinking
it looks a little weird
I was thinking
should I add a collar
or make it longer
or add a hat
I was thinking
what should I do
then I thought about it
forget it
make it longer
after making it longer
I felt
the shawl looks good
it looks good
the shawl is a little short
so it doesn't have the right shape
after I tried it
it looks like
it has the right shape
the shape is right
then because of the expansion of the panel
the shawl
won't look good
so I changed it
with the edge shawl
then I will compare it again
to see if the effect I want
is like this
oh
then
then I added a pair of gloves
this glove is
the one I used to make
the dress
I will change the layers
After I put on the gloves, I feel like the smell is getting more and more right
Except that she didn't wear high heels
And then I took it off
I feel like this kind of clothes all have silk socks
Otherwise the legs feel like they are shiny
Then I drew a silk sock board
Then I also put on the model's heels
Because I thought she was going to wear high heels later
Then I took this silk sock to compare the length
Then I still prefer to have an absolute collar
So I still shortened its length a little
This is actually compared to the model in this 2D
Our model's cut and then do
Then add some pins
After adding pins
You can see
I put her
The shrinkage has been increased
Increased shrinkage is to be able to quickly put this silk sock on the outside of our model
When you look at the promotional picture
She didn't seem to put my silk socks in
But this set of clothes is actually with silk socks
Then I feel that this shrinkage is that I put the shrinkage to 200%
After that, I think this board should be able to fit the model's feet
Then I deleted the pins
Then I want to say that I put these two pieces of cloth outside the model
Then add some pins to determine its position
Then reduce the particle diameter
Because the model's net grid is relatively large
Then our board if the particle diameter is 20
It's hard to put it on the outside of this foot
So I will reduce its particle diameter to 10 first
Just reduced to
I remember testing it before
Anyway, if it's reduced to 5, it's a bit too laggy
Let's use 10 first
Then I will change its height
The reason for this is because
Now the model's feet are standing on the ground
If the height of the ground is 0
This board
You put it on the ground
She can't pull it down anymore
The silk sock itself has a certain thickness
So I will change the height of this net grid
Let me pull this
Let me pull this silk sock
It will be more convenient
Is not it
This method is actually learned by everyone
Just pull it little by little
The process seems to be very strange
But you will find it very convenient later
This function
Because it's pretty fast
Then I will apply a new fabric to it
Then I will adjust its gold tail gauze
And the angle of the right foot line to be lower
Thank you
In this way
This fabric is easier to stretch
Because of the default fabric itself
Its stretch performance is
Although it can
But it's not as good as silk socks
Then just this silk sock
Isn't its shrink rate 200%?
Then I will change its shrink rate to 120%
Change to 120
Because at this time
It can fit the model curve a little bit
Then it won't be too tight
In fact, the main thing is that I want
The sole of the foot is more likely to penetrate
I just want to flatten it first
Then at this time
The example can be reduced to 5
Because you almost have a rough shape
Then at 5
I found that its toes will still penetrate
So I may reduce it to 4
Then adjust the tail to 100%
That is to say
Let him
This sock
This board
Can match our model
Match the original size
Then go to drag it
Then you can see it now
This silk sock is basically
It's already wrapped around our model
Is it very convenient?
You don't need to use those
What kind of editing grid
What tools
Then it's hard to pull
Then in fact
There is a little gap here
That is, I found this sock
Why can't I pull it up
Then I
I just can't imagine
Why can't this sock be pulled up
Let's take a test
I didn't ask him in advance
Do you know why my socks can't be pulled up?
You take a look
The information in this picture
The chats can also guess
Why can't I pull up my socks?
Let me think
I can't let the chats see
The chats can guess
Why this sock is
I can't hang it down
I can't pull it up
If I do
I may first
On the silk sock
Just what you said
The one you can't pull up
Add a elastic on the board
Try it
See if you can maintain that shape
Then try it again
Pull it up
Take a look
Add a elastic
Is it a straight elastic?
Or is it an extra 100 elastic?
Just keep
The elastic must be adjusted to 100
Then maintain the original length of this line
Let me see
See if there is
I see the kimchi net
The kimchi net is the one that is right
Yes
Too smart
Little friends
In fact, the reason is
Because I added a elastic on it
The top of my mouth
Added a elastic of 60
Here
Too smart
Little friends
Because of the trap on it
Then I was still drooling
I thought for a long time
I said
Tingting
This is not right
What's going on
I
This silk sock
Other places are perfect
Why can't this be pulled up?
Give me a hurry
Then I used a sewing machine again
Use a fixing needle again
Fixing needle
What I was thinking at that time
I add two rows of fixing needles below
Then release the upper shrinkage
Then I feel like a fool
Because I have added elasticity
Why do you say I add this fixing needle?
Then I was
Forget it
It's okay
Just add the fixing needle
Don't
I'm not familiar with you
Speaking of pineapple rice
Who proposed last time
Let us cooperate with pineapple rice
Then I went to ask pineapple rice
People don't like our MD
This may be
The humble MD
Then do it well on one side
Just copy the other side
That's how this silk sock is done
In fact, silk socks are still more convenient
Let me see
Let's speed up this video
Because in fact
There is nothing behind
Everything else is relatively simple
The silk socks don't fall
There is another reason
Maybe I added that
Added that
Add friction coefficient
There is another one
I will go to this silk sock
Add some fixing needles on the circle
Then select it
Fixed to the virtual model
Then there is a bug here
That is, you add to the virtual model
After going to the model
This one
It's going to get thicker
But it doesn't matter
You can simulate it
Add the fixing needle to the model
There is an advantage
Just as you go to change these poses
This silk sock will not fall down
Then I will add a small rectangle to it
I sew it up
Because I'm thinking about hanging two balls on it
Do you add another circle to the fur of the cloak?
Yes
There will be a demonstration later
Then add a small line
Make it a little hollow in the middle
I may be thinking about it later
Oh, it's here
The circle I asked
I will use the string tool
Then along our circle
I will add a small circle
Then add a small circle
Then use the struggling tool
Then along the outside of our cloak
Then and create a circle
Make sure the ring is at the end
Then let him finish at the end
After completion
Fix it
There will be a circle like this channel shaped
签条工具其实我最常用到的都是用来做这个,一圈毛毛编。
菠萝饭摊可是很牛的大佬,期待你们的合作。
是呀,你们要,这个问题是你们要去问菠萝大佬,不是,不是我们的问题哦。
就先甩锅给菠萝,哦,不是我们的问题哦。
还有其他的一些,哦,然后前面我把这个钱中合并了。
合并完了之后,大家会看到归拔会没有啊,所以大家就是一定要谨记,你如果要合并的话就早点合并。
归拔是一旦你对版片进行了一些裁剪啊,合并,这个归拔就没有了。
然后再归一下,再归一下之后我就想说加一些钮扣吧。
哎,我感觉好像这些衣服上面都会有一些钮扣,
然后我这是要做什么,哦,我在做那个毛线球的那个,坠下来的那两根绳子。
哦,欠条是本身就没有闭合的。
欠条,所以说你看我把欠条就放在这个后中那里,因为它没有闭合。
这个是我们之前已经提过功能开发需求了。
但是可能开发起来还是有一些难度,让那个网格合并。
所以我都会把这个欠条的位置藏在看不到的地方。
然后就是把这个毛线球的两根绳子放回去,哎,缩率百分百。
是吗?
是,这,这都被你逮到了。
我好像记得我中间偷偷把那个缩率改回去还是干嘛。
然后在我这个做,做完这两个绳子之后呢,我就会把这个毛线球,我本来想做毛线球嘛,就把这个珍珠。
就把这个珍珠,就是反正你们经常会见到的那个东西,那个圆球。
我基本上每一个,每一期直播都会把它放进去。
我也不知道为什么,可能因为我只会做球吧。
就是和大家只会拉box是一样的。
然后我就会更换姿势。
然后就可以看到Hana就在慢慢慢慢慢慢慢慢改她的姿势。
然后因为有固定针固定针,我可以看到她的姿势。
然后因为有固定针固定针虚拟模特嘛,所以其实这个袜子是会跟着我们模特走的。
这也是为什么我的袜子从来不会掉下来的原因。
然后之后,哦,我因为这个手套板片其实做的有点问题,然后我就觉得在Hana的小小的手上面显得这个手套,特别的粗壮。
And then, because I made some problems with the gloves, I thought that the gloves on Hana's hands were too thick, and her fingers were also too thick, so I decided to cut the gloves.
After cutting, I deleted these, so that it looks like the gloves that some children wear when they go to school.
After making the gloves, I felt that because of this posture, about this posture,
when I was adjusting the model's posture,
I hoped that Hana would have that kind of feeling,
that is to say,
since there is no one to accompany you on Christmas,
why don't you just spend time with me?
And then, it's the feeling of wanting to pull your hand.
And then I thought about it,
in that kind of youth romance,
when a girl usually wants to hold someone else's hand,
she won't wear gloves.
She might take off the gloves.
And then,
use her hand to warm up your palm.
Anyway, at that time, I was thinking about some weird plot twists.
And then I thought,
then I'll take off the gloves on this hand.
in general, if you take off the gloves,
you might put them in the belt.
And then I changed it there.
I thought about folding the gloves into her belt.
I took off the gloves inside the belt.
And then,
in some ways,
Hana was able to adjust the posture.
And then,
the two of you,
you both made some changes.
For example,
I made a change in the body shape.
But you didn't change it suddenly,
right?
You both made some changes.
And then,
I said,
you did a little bit of some adjustments,
I did a little bit of some adjustment.
And then,
I made some changes inside the belt.
then,
I made some adjustments
inside the belt,
The level of the belt is 2, and the level of the gloves is 1, so that the gloves can be worn in this way.
It turns out that you have to think about these things to learn how to make clothes.
Well, it's not like that. How can I say?
In general, every set of clothes that I make, including their movements,
the movements that I have adjusted for you,
I usually consider them to be more in line with the theme.
Because the promotional pictures we make are usually close-up.
So I want to say that every time the movements are different.
In the past, at the beginning, I might have done some more close-up movements.
And now that Hana is out, I'm starting to let go of myself.
I think Hana is very beautiful no matter how you look at it.
Any posture suits her very well.
So I will try to do some for her.
The posture she does is actually what I see in a beautiful girl warrior.
There is a water soldier who turns his head.
Anyway, there is a cartoon screenshot.
He turns his head and looks at you with his mask.
And then I adjusted this posture.
It's a little similar to her movement.
That's about it.
We're done with this thing.
Then I added a little bit of material to it.
And then the final effect is
Someone can show off directly in MD.
What she uses is not MD.
She uses another software in our company.
It's called CLO.
CLO and MD are different.
CLO is for rendering.
Fixed to model.
Fixed needle.
Wait a minute.
Let me look at this project file.
Let me freeze the other parts first.
Actually, for example, I have a circle of board here.
And then.
Choose the grid to match.
Fixed needle.
Comparison.
For example, add a circle of fixed needles here.
Then right click.
There is a fixed needle.
Fixed to the virtual model.
Well, then.
It will move with the virtual model.
Clothes in the well.
Generally, there will be problems with the color.
You can add a lot of fixed needles.
After adding a fixed needle.
It will apply the thickness of the collision.
So you may have to simulate it after adding a fixed needle.
In fact, you put this fabric attribute.
Click on the details below.
There is a friction coefficient below.
This is also a translation error.
The friction coefficient is adjusted.
When it is simulated with your model.
There will also be this.
Changed with the model.
Well.
Then here.
Our Christmas.
This is the first part of the special.
About this Hannah's clothes.
This part is done.
Then.
Speaking of which.
Do you remember?
We had a competition before.
It's 3D.
It's.
That one.
Yes.
The little competition of the chess temple.
This little competition.
It's not a big competition.
It's a small competition.
Everyone.
Just.
Interested in the competition.
I can only say.
Originally.
Tonight.
Is to announce the award list.
But.
Well.
There are some friends.
They said.
Oh.
Why are you so late?
There is this.
This game.
I have already.
I didn't participate.
Well.
Then we decided temporarily.
Do you want to extend it again?
This.
Game.
It's the deadline.
Then.
Everyone.
In the previous.
B station dynamic.
May have already seen.
There is a set.
It's more complicated than this set of clothes.
And then the action.
Also.
A beautiful one.
Hannah's.
A set of clothes.
That is.
As a reward.
To give our top three.
So everyone.
Now.
If you still want to participate.
You can.
Send an email.
To my mailbox.
Sherry.
At.
Marvelousdesigner.com
Inside.
Just.
In short.
We are workers.
Uh.
Everyone.
To have a job.
Uh.
In.
It is.
The time.
Time.
Or.
Usually.
Everyone.
Uh.
The student party.
Can.
Come.
Participate in the game.
Unlimited.
Video.
And pictures.
How to participate.
So.
Uh.
This game.
The deadline.
It has been.
Played until the end of January.
Uh.
The first.
There will be a year.
Marvelousdesigner.
Ten.
Use.
And then.
Uh.
The second.
There will be three months.
Uh.
In short.
You can't buy it.
Can't buy it.
Anyway.
It's okay.
Just come and participate.
As long as it can show.
New functions.
Useful place.
Uh.
Whether it's a picture.
Or a video.
All right.
High heels.
Is.
Self-support.
Look at the picture.
Look at.
The picture.
I'm in this.
I don't seem to have it.
I'm in.
Because this one is live.
Use.
Or say.
Want to see.
The rendering of this dress.
Is there.
Should.
No.
It doesn't seem to be.
Oh.
I really didn't come over.
Crashed.
I cracked.
In.
Anyway.
It's possible on the official website.
Uh.
Not official website.
It's in that.
Bilibili.
It can be seen.
It's okay now.
Can.
Participate.
Then.
Uh.
The first part.
We're almost there.
And then.
Next.
Is our second part.
It's about us.
This.
Some summary of this year's live broadcast.
Then.
I'll follow the order.
Show you.
What we've been live broadcasting this year.
Some.
Content.
And then.
Uh.
Every project file.
Will stay for a few minutes.
And then.
You have something about this.
Some questions about the project file.
You can ask.
New features.
Is.
Is there any interest in the hair line sticker?
Right.
The hair line sticker.
One is in our UV editor.
You can do a baking.
And then.
The other one is in the file.
When you export OBJ.
We can choose to.
Uh.
Here.
Based on 3D.
To bake the hair line.
Is.
In the previous version.
Our.
This.
Here.
It can't be exported.
These.
Shadows.
In the new version.
It can be exported.
Shadows.
MAMAMOOLESS DESIGNER's live stream
The live stream wasn't recorded like this
It was done live
So I was a bit nervous
The whole process was to make a set
A set that would match their
Little model's
Backpack
And this
Clothes
Do you have any questions about this set?
If you have any questions, you can ask them in the comments
I'll answer them if I see them
The main process of making this set is
To change the pattern
To make the pattern fit our model's body line
And also
When making these pants
We'll use something like
For example
A
Folding tool
To fold the pants up
And also
Actually these
Pockets
I made them all with MD
I made them all with the pattern
What does it mean that the Substance Painter broke it?
Obviously
If you watched our company's live stream last year
If you watch the live stream of another software
You'll find that
I was also there in the first live stream
So actually
We actually had this idea of live streaming earlier
But we didn't find a good opportunity
To tell everyone
We now have this live stream plan
And so on
So actually last year
This was also last year's January
Not last year
January of this year
A live stream made a year ago
The download of the pattern can't be downloaded
Just
Open it up a little bit
And then just download it
How to add the metal buckle
The metal buckle
I added it in the form of an add-on
It's an add-on
So you'll see
There will be some holes
And then during the process
I might go and adjust
The position of this add-on
Or to adjust
The position of this button
And then I might
Turn off the conflict between this button
In this way
It won't have that kind of
Uh
Penetration problem
And then this panel
It's actually a little bit wider than the original panel
It's just that it's in the middle of this panel
This piece
I might increase its length a little bit
So you'll have
Uh, when you add a metal buckle
And then this is where it's going to pop up
And then this metal material
I gave it directly in MD
And then if you want to pour it out
When you pour it out
Uh, you can bake it
When this metal paint is poured out
It will bring the effect of the metal
Um
The sticker is not
How do you do the stickers in MD
I'm just looking for the stickers outside
Uh, these are all textiles
Yes, the metal buckle made of the panel
This is actually a square panel
You can see it
It has that kind of panel making trace
Dig a hole in the middle
And then there are those
What is it
Uh, what is this called
Corrugation of edges and so on
And then this one is also
This one is also a
Uh, it's just a strip
Because my 3D modeling is not very good
So what I can do in MD
It's all done in MD
And then this is the first one
Then let's jump to the next one
The second one
Uh, the second one is actually
In the real sense
It's a live broadcast made by MD himself
At that time
Uh, because of the epidemic
Uh, this live broadcast video is prepared by the company
Then we go back to
Uh, the office here
Start
After work
Uh, the company said
Do you want to make a uniform
Then
Flight suit
This is the first episode I made
Is
Um
No cooperation with others
A set of clothes made
Then at that time
At this time
In fact, it's just a video
It's not live on the spot anymore
Yeah, this one
These contents are actually in this
Um
Our
This
There are these live broadcasts in the channel
So you can take a look
I don't know if you have any questions about this set of clothes
Uh, this set of clothes
When I was doing it
In fact, there is also
Um, there is no reference picture
Uh, in general
It's all in my head
Think about it
What kind of
For example
Because at that time
They said they wanted me to do that
A little pilot style
The pilot
There may be a set inside
Uh
It's a chain of clothes
So I'll do it first
This circle inside
Chain
Then these ties are added at the back
And then finally
This jacket on this layer outside
Shoes are self-adjusted
Shoes are self-adjusted models
And then these are my home pins
Just because
In order to prevent this
Clothes from coming out
Because of the shoes
He has a net
In fact
It's going to have a conflict with the version
And then like this
You can see
The one I'm wearing outside
In fact, it's all made by the version
And then through different patterns
Let him have one
Um, the back
A belt
Uh, the effect of the jacket
Fixed
Oh, this half is indeed
And then this half
Because it's a special
So I've been fixing it
And then in the new version
He always comes out
Because of some strange reasons
So, um, maybe
This
This question
We have also responded
I hope that in the future
The pudding version
Can solve this question
This set of clothes
Like this version
You can see
It's actually very simple
I'm usually just
Uh, just draw a board
And then use a fixed needle
Stick it here
And then here
I'll use a fixed needle
Stick it here
Um, after that
Then gradually
Add these details to him
For example
This bag
And here
Sew it up
And then I might
I will also refer to
Um, in real life
Do this
Bag
It may have a double-layer structure
Then I will put it here
His double-layer performance
Open it
Then there is
Is it folded in here?
I will fold it in
The shoes follow the action
Or do the shoes first
Uh, shoes
The shoes in MD
Is our own
It's our software
If you change the action
He will follow your model
Change it
But if you are
It's the same
If you are
You can change it
It's the same
But if you are
If you are
Uh, do it yourself
I suggest it
Does the shoe make a single OBJ
In other software
Is
Well adjust
Its position
Then в
Then last to model mode
Then wear it
Uh, if you use MD's default model
The shoes will follow the model
Then this set of clothes
Do you have any other questions
Another is
Uh, this set
The key point of making this kind of tie is that the friction coefficient will be improved by us.
The reason why I didn't improve the friction coefficient is that I wanted it to be alone.
Then I found that it didn't seem to fall down, so I didn't change its friction coefficient.
The red line on the board, do you mean this kind of line?
It is an internal line, and its function is one.
You can change the folding angle so that it will have a kind of this line.
The effect of hooking in along this line, or you can sew the board up.
Look at my board, it has a red internal line here, and a red internal line below.
By creating a sewing line between the line and the line,
you can make this dress, oh, not a dress,
just let the board be sewn to another board.
Do you think there will be separate friction coefficient hooking in the future?
Instead of a single pixel size?
Oh, um, maybe, maybe there will be.
I can mention this.
Functional development needs, separate friction coefficient hooking.
Right.
This internal line is usually,
the reason why the password of our group is the internal line,
is because the function of the internal line is really,
often, it's not often, it's like a resource for everything.
You need to add an internal line for everything you do.
You need to add an internal line for sewing,
you need to add an internal line for folding,
and then, um, you need to add an internal line for sewing.
Like this.
And then we go to the next one.
The next picture is like this.
This is his 30 picture.
And then this is a rendering picture.
At that time, we received a response from everyone,
saying that at that time,
everyone wanted to know how to make hanfu.
So we held a live broadcast,
live broadcast of making hanfu.
So we held a live broadcast of making hanfu.
And then, um, this project file looks a little big.
It took a little while to open,
because the stickers I added on top are a little big.
At that time,
it means that everyone wanted to know more about,
um, how to make hanfu.
So the main content of this live broadcast is,
uh, how I design these panels.
And then, in fact, these panels have no design.
The panels of hanfu are all very simple.
They're all rectangular.
And then there's this big sleeve.
And then there's another one outside.
And it also includes this, um,
a stronger one,
and a stronger one.
And then what about this?
Does anyone have any questions about this?
This set of hanfu.
Oh, right.
It's me on the LINE app.
Then,
yes, it's our MD official and the LINE app together.
They have,
yes,
or someone is watching this video.
I posted this video on Bilibili.
There's a post on it.
How do you make it stand up?
When you sew it up, it stands up by itself.
Then for the fabric, you may have to set it up separately.
You have to increase its bending strength a little bit.
So that it won't fall down.
Because when the bending strength is very high, it will be like that kind of hard leather.
You can think about it.
It's hard leather. It's not easy to hammer it down.
And then it itself will have some hardness.
So when you sew it up to the inner line of the top of the shirt,
it will stand up.
And then this color combination.
Actually, I also considered this color combination.
Why did I say that the Hanfu I made would choose this kind of shoulder armor?
One is that sometimes people will ask how to make this kind of shoulder armor.
I think this kind of small shoulder armor
can still be made with fabric in MD.
You may not be able to make a large shoulder armor.
How do you add a background picture?
In the 3D background, right click.
Then there is an increase background picture.
Then click it and you can add a background picture.
Little Bun doesn't usually draw his own version.
He made his own version.
Yes.
Then when I made this set of clothes,
I just thought that I didn't want to make such an ordinary Hanfu.
Then I want to say that I want to add some design to it.
Then I added a shoulder armor to it.
The main one is that I was thinking at that time.
Who is wearing Hanfu?
Because I don't seem to know much about Hanfu.
Then I think that
this kind of special fairy style Hanfu.
It's just that the steps may be very short.
So it's very long.
Then everyone generally wants to do Hanfu.
I want to know how to do it like this big sleeve.
Then like this big sleeve.
We usually change the model's posture to a special T pose.
That is, the two hands cross over.
Then just put the whole piece of board here.
Then sew it to change its action.
There is a screen.
The bending intensity on the material is actually the fabric.
Is it easy to bend?
Then this material is the higher the attribute.
The more the fabric is not easy to bend,
the more it can maintain its original hardness.
You can imagine.
That is to say, the higher the bending intensity,
the harder this board will be.
That hard board.
When you pinch it,
it will be straight.
It won't fall down.
The dragon pattern on the clothes.
I actually added a phoenix on my clothes.
Not a dragon.
That's because it's not yellow.
Then I use a sticker tool.
Put this board on top of these dragon patterns.
Oh phoenix pattern.
The phoenix pattern that was brought over.
Then I usually add it.
The habit is that I like it.
Like this side will leave some gaps.
Then the closer to the bottom,
I will add more to it.
Some of these patterns.
How to add the posture.
The posture is Shift X.
A posture that I adjusted myself.
In MD,
Open Shift X.
You can open this default model's Google.
Or you yourself.
The model you love.
Is an Alembic file.
Or FBX file.
It has its own Google.
Then you can change these Google.
Then in the clothes itself.
In the case of T-pose.
Let it change little by little.
To the posture you want.
In the process of changing.
The clothes will slowly.
Change with the movement.
Semi-transparent sand on hand.
Semi-transparent sand is.
When I was in T-pose.
Just add it directly.
After adding it.
I will use this fake sewing needle.
Put this.
Put this sand.
And clothes.
Like this.
Click, click.
Sew together.
Then when you change the movement.
It will not.
There are some friction.
Changes.
And this fabric.
I may be in advance.
Its.
The friction coefficient is adjusted.
Then it.
After changing the movement.
Change back.
Then.
You can see me.
This side.
It will have a pile effect.
It's because I used to.
Will give this.
This bag.
Use a shrink.
For example.
Its tail shrink.
I will change to 80.
After changing to 80.
This fabric.
It will not shrink.
Shrink.
Then I will give it.
Add some pins on both sides.
Then put the middle part.
Separately.
Let go.
It will have.
This kind of.
The wrinkle effect.
How to make the pattern.
Hit a butterfly knot.
In general.
We are.
Here.
Is.
Will divide the butterfly knot.
Into many parts.
For example.
The butterfly knot.
It has two ears.
There are two down.
Two down.
That's a total of four pieces.
Then add the position of the knot in the middle.
A total of five pieces.
Then we will use.
Um.
The pattern.
To simulate this.
The effect of these five pieces.
Can the model's face be changed into his own face?
You can change it with PS.
Don't.
You can.
You can change it.
UV.
You can change it into your own face.
But the bone.
It's still this bone.
The pattern doesn't change.
That's the first step.
You can change it so that it's not the same as the normal pattern.
The second step.
You can change it.
Do it again.
It's still the same.
It's just a little bit.
The second step.
The third step.
The fourth step.
Under this color.
I want to change it.
So you can do this.
The fourth step.
Hope that it can be changed.
It's the third.
Yes.
Can you do it?
This is the third one.
No.
Back to this one.
This one.
The third one.
This.
No.
Fix it to the virtual model
You can fix your clothes on your virtual model
The image resolution is changed to 40
Just don't need to adjust the version
But in this case
Your grid is still a lot
Still big
Right?
Your grid number will increase
Because the resolution just makes your grid smaller
But it won't reduce your grid number
Let's look at the next one
The next one is June
In June
This is the rendering
In June, a lot of friends asked
I always see you as a human model
Can you do something that looks different?
Then I asked our boss to help me find a model
Finally, I found such a model
In fact, it doesn't look like this
Right?
She didn't give her face
This kind of strange
This one with a little mirror next to me
She looks very Buddhist
Then I don't know why
Anyway, I looked at this model at that time
I think this model is very suitable for some
Just
Very
Very eerie styles
Then I gave her
Draw a little bit
Her this
I just
I feel that the speed can be used directly
Can be used
If you want to do the expansion effect
Add pressure
After choosing the fabric
There is a pressure here
Just add it up
Then
At that time, anyway
Because I myself also like to see those
Murderer
Rejection
Horror movie
People like this
I thought at that time
Because I originally wanted to do
The set of clothes of the Little Mermaid
But I think that the set of clothes
Will definitely be found
This is not the Silver set of Little Mermaid
The set of clothes of the Little Mermaid
Then I thought
Forget it
I will change it a little
Just have that kind of
The feeling of a little thief in the circus
How to draw the face
The face is to draw
Draw her
This material picture
You see
This is her material picture
Just draw her UV
In fact, I used to have her
Other
Is
There is this UV
I just went alone
In the PS
I dealt with this face
Then
Through some
Glowing effect
Then
You can make her
This face that was originally very Buddha
There will be that kind of
A relatively dark feeling
I remember I hit four or five lights at that time
Just I feel that kind of
The clown in the movie
Just the kind of
People who look like bad guys
Their lighting is generally
More gloomy
Then
It's usually darker
No main light
Then there is only that kind of
UU
It's the kind of TV that will be released at night
There is red again
There is green
And a little purple
Those lights
The clown is me
Falling ball
Fall
Falling ball is
This is a board
Then I sewed it inside
Then this ball
I added a weight to it
Here I added her
30 grams of weight
That itself
This board
Her physical properties
Her physical properties are
These physical properties are the most common
Then she is
That is, she may be like this
Hey
It won't fall down
But once you add this ball to her
Then she will fall down
Because this ball has gravity
Then there will be this kind of clown
I see
Don't they have hats
There will be some decorations on the neck
The wrinkle on the waist is not pulled out
Is this waist board itself
The body shape of this board and the model is not in line
And then when I sewed it
It seems to be
Let her specifically
There are some differences in sewing here
Or you said it was the skirt
This is because of the board
The board
This board is bigger than this piece of board
Then sew them together
There will be this kind of
This kind of wrinkle effect
How does the ball connect with the board
Click on the ball
Then click on this glue tool
Then you can stick it on
Then you open the model again
This ball will
Just through that point
Then take this board down
Print the board and show it
You just put this
Then increase its properties
Increase its bending strength
It will stand up
Because my project file is relatively card
Do a print
Then do it
I think it will be very card
I want to put this
I want to put this ball
Put it
Don't move it
Change its weight to zero
Or just stick it somewhere else
Why don't you move
I didn't see you
I feel like I met some bug
I really met a bug
You see it is moving
As a result, it will not turn over in a while
Xiwenlejie turned over
Wow
Turned over, brothers
I already feel that this version
How to hang out
Haha
I am the clown
It doesn't matter
Does he give it a chance?
Hurry up
Help him manually
I am angry
Change the fabric for him
Turn it off
Go to the past
Can you do it?
Just tick it off
You saw it
If you don't know how to do it,
I have a free ability
It's fake
I can't turn it on
If you want to
And then again
I don't know how to do it
Don't want to
So he can't
Turn off
I planned
I can't
I don't know
I don't need to
I just want to
I just can't
It's really easy
I can do it
I can easily
Don't mess up
Like this
I have it in the MD8 new features demonstration video
Let's see if it won't move now
Let it be here
Let's hurry to the next one
I'm afraid that you guys will let me do some weird things again
And then it will be even better
But to be honest, my boss told me before
Actually, my friends all like to watch me flip cars
Okay okay okay, then let's flip the car
And then this is the little curse
So actually when you guys are making clothes
You can think about whether it can be made in the MD
Actually, all kinds of clothes can be made
Wow, this is also good
This is our Crytek
You can see that I will start to make some clothes for you guys
That I haven't tried before
For example, like this boots
Boots were also made at that time
Then include this front bag
This front bag, you can see that this version is actually very simple
It's just a circle
Then add a circle of elastic to this mouth
It will form a kind of cloth bag effect
Then there will be some threads on the belt above
On this belt
And then at that time
Crytek and I had a collaboration
It's about making clothes for hunters
That is, the first few players in the competition
Can be put in the game and will actually be used
Threads? What kind of thread?
The same clothes as before?
Then there is no thread on that piece of clothing
Hi, hello, hello
Hello
Then when making this piece of clothing
In fact, the pattern is not very difficult
I always take a T-shirt
Just change it here and there
Then add some elastic
Let him draw more wrinkles here
Then how does the rope hang up?
The rope is like this
In fact, my rope is divided into two
These two are actually
It shouldn't be entangled together
It seems to be entangled
Then the other one is directly copied
One is entangled with a fixed needle
I'll make a section first
It's about this long
From here to here
Fixed needle
Not a fixed needle plate
Then put it
With a fixed needle like this
Pull this plate a little longer
Then wrap it around the belt needle
Finally, sew it together with this plate
Just good
Really
The sole is also a plate
This knot is also a knot
I remember I was the first to hit the knot
So you can see that it is a whole plate
Very powerful
I remember this one
The waist is not tied
I was divided into two
Two plates to play
Finally put the back side together
The rope is actually not difficult to control
The rope is
How do you say
You have to be patient
A little bit with a fixed needle
Pull it a little longer
Then adjust a little
Then pull it a little longer
Just adjust a little
I still use this belt
It should be used for some friction techniques
And the effect of the belt to hit the fixed needle
I still prefer
Just pull it with a fixed needle
Some knot effects
I think it's more real
It's okay
The strap is connected to the rope
Just sew it
There are two internal lines here
You can't see it
There are two internal lines
Then sew it up
That's it
What about the old Sichuan
Put the plate
Reduce the particle diameter of the plate
Then increase the friction
Then don't pull the plate too much
You have to treat it gently
In the words of the people in the group
Is to ask you to treat the model
Is to treat the model
Don't go hard
Not not not BJ
Not just a round plate
Round plate
Then it was originally a circle
Right
Then add a circle of fixed needles here
After
Where did I add a circle of fixed needles
It seems to be here
Added a circle of fixed needles
Then add a circle of elasticity to it here
You can see that the elasticity here
May only be 10%
Because the pocket is tightened here
Can imagine
This circle of edge
It will tighten in
Then add
After this elasticity of 10
It will shrink by itself
It will shrink into a bag by itself
This method is also more convenient
Everyone is usually
Anyway, no matter what you do
Including some of the modern clothes
If you are a decoration
You can also give him a bag like this
Do you have books on the board?
No
I usually think about what to do
Search online
Then next is
Before with Juefei
Do a joint live
A project file in the field
This file
Is a set of home
Because it was asked
Juefei is
Is there anything you want to know
In MD
Can be done
It's a relatively rare thing
Look at this swallow button
How does the swallow button do it
There are some in the video
Then this swallow button project file
I sent it to the QQ group
You didn't go down
This swallow button is
Just
Draw a board
Then draw a few circles with the internal line on it
Then you sew a very thin rope on it
Just like you
Just use that
Because the swallow button is not made of limited silk
You just take the paper as
Just draw a board
As the paper you put the fabric
Then draw the internal line
As the way you roll
In short, there will be in that live broadcast
There is that explanation
Then how to insert the paper of the waist
Just freeze all the boards
Then put the paper of the waist in
Just like making gloves today
Then I asked Juefei
He said he wanted to know
How to do this
Do what
Make furniture
He said he saw some furniture companies
They may use MD
Then I said
Then just do it
Make furniture
Then
Then I made a set of this furniture
All these things
Except for these two balls
I really just every
Every project file will use this ball
Except for this ball
Everything else is made by MD
Including this bed
Then in that video
Also to everyone
Introduce how to make this bed
And this bed head
This kind of
One of the effects of sleeping
The swallow button
Yes, the board is done
Then OBJ poured in
Then
How to do this bed
It was also mentioned in that live broadcast
Also includes this pillow
In fact, it is
Then this pillow
The one wrapped in it
The stick is also made in MD
Anyway, I can do it with the board
I basically don't use
Do it in other ways
Just lazy
Why
MD can make balls
It's just that the ball
It's not so round
Is
I don't know
The live broadcast next door
Have you seen it
The lampshade
I used to do it with the board
Just
Do it more
It's more troublesome
It's better to go out directly
Pour a ball body
It's more convenient to come in
More smooth
How to make a ball
The ball is opened by 3D
Open 3D Max
Then
Open that ball
Then you pull one
Not in MD
If you really want to know
The ball is to draw two
Round board
Up and down
Then put them
All material properties are adjusted to 0
Except
Except for the deformation rate
All adjusted to 0
Then add
Add to the positive pressure
Add to 50
Then these two boards
Will be
Boom
Become
Just
It's like a balloon blown up
But not so round
Ball
The particle monitor
Is the inflator
The inflator comes out of the ball
Yes
It can inflate and inflate the ball
But that ball
It's not very round
Then if you want to make it round
Then you have to give it
There is a fixing needle on top
Then let it down below
Then turn it over
Turn the whole ball over
Then let the bottom
Use gravity to make it round
This method is actually very troublesome
So you say
It's so troublesome
You might as well go to 3D Max
Pull one
How fast is that
Right
Why do you have to challenge yourself?
Although others can be stolen
But this one
This one really doesn't work
This one
Or don't steal
You pull a circle
How big is a ball
Then add one
Is
Oh
Yes
Then
In fact
I also added a curtain on top
There is a curtain
And this background
In fact, they are all
It fits in MD
Then
The light in this rendering
Also uses that ball
Then
It's still that ball
Give it a glow material
Let it look like a light
In fact, it's still that ball
Okay, don't learn what it is
Just 3D
3D Max
3D Maya
Blender
ZBrush
Marvelous Designer
Closed
So I think this last rendering picture is still
I still like the effect
I think it looks pretty good
It's pretty good
Including color matching
What
Then in fact
At first
There is no round light
The original rendering picture
It's very dark
Then
Our boss
After watching this
Tell me
He said
Who do you see
This
Sleeping room
Is it so dark
I said
Yes
My own room
It's so dark
Then my boss said
You hurry up and add two lights for me
I said
Oh, good, good, good
How to fold the bedding
It's not folded in
Uh, this bedding is actually
It's pulled out
It's not folded in
It was originally a flat board
And then
On top of that
I will add
These round internal lines
Then you sew it
After that
Rushing pressure
Uh
Because of the pressure
This function
These small boards
The board in the middle
Very few
I can't stick it together
But the ones next to it
It's going to stick together
So
It's not
So it's like this after it's done
It's like this
It's sticking together
And then this board
In fact, it's
This is a very thick board
So it looks like it's in the middle
It's like it's stuck in
In fact
Uh, no
In fact, this board is thicker
And then the last one is
Uh
November
In November
We
Uh
Actually
It's a new feature
New feature
This live
Uh
It's also
We introduced the new features first
And then
Uh
Yu Yizhu
Let me show you
She made
Make a shoe with MD
And then
At that time
Actually
I don't know if you have seen it
Uh
That's what we're doing
This
Uh
When the micro-channel is posted
In fact, I made a dress
Uh
The information of this dress
I sent it to the group
And then
The production process
It's also sent to the group
In fact
It's really fast to make a dress
Uh
Not long
I spent most of my time
On this glove
Then
At that time, I also put a little pumpkin
I don't know why
I come over
This project
Pumpkin is gone
Uh
Then
At that time
Because it's going to be Christmas
Then
In fact
The new version
Has not been released yet
Ah
I just
It's like a sneak run for everyone
We have a new model
Then
As a model for Hana
Made a set of Christmas clothes
And
I think
Later
It's not a good idea
I think
It's more like
This
I see
You're not going to be able to make any more
I
I see
I'm not going to be able to make more
Actually
I also
Like
I
Don't mind
but
It's a bit
Yeah
I'll take care of it
Let's see
I've been working on it for two years
from now
I think
it's okay
Do you think
It's okay
and put it next to it
If you plug it in, it will glow
If you don't plug it in, it won't glow
The wax is cool
This headband is really simple
You just sew it on both sides
Here is a fold
After the fold, you sew it on both sides
It's a headband
Or you say this
This is more simple
This is a circle
This is a rectangular
You sew it up, it's a circle
You sew it up
It's a headband
This chain is
Made in MD
This is all board
So you can imagine how lazy I am
This board
Is all here
It's a circle
And in the middle
I added a bigger circle
And I made a hexagon
Like this
This is
At that time, it was Halloween
And in fact, in the company
I used this headband on Slack
I really like this
I remember I was looking at
A new version
And there was a nun in it
So I thought
Let's make a bad nun on Halloween
And in fact
It doesn't have much to do with nuns
Let me show you the chain
My computer is lagging
It's just two rings
You put it together
And then you simulate it
And then you change all of its physical properties
To 100
Just the first few
All adjusted to 100
And then the rest is all 0
You simulate it again
It's like this
This chain needs to be put together for a while
If I say
It's just because I don't know how to use 3D Max
To make chains
I won't use AMD to make chains
How troublesome
This can do
You can't do animation calculation
This will
I tried it when I was doing the action
This chain will fall apart
Instead of doing this
It's better to use this copy
Just set it to this position
Let it not move
Otherwise
It can only be used as a mirror
If you do animation
This chain is unbearable
Instead of doing this chain
It's better to make a plate
And then you put the chain
In the form of a copy
Set it on the transparent plate
It can be a little better
This is
There is no video
Although I recorded the video
Because it involves Hana
Then I
The video is not clear
I didn't do it
Chain chain
It has nothing to do with the inflator
It's just a single small plate
And then add thickness
I added the rendering thickness to it
So it looks like a chain
Chain chain
The effect
Yizijianji 1
Only this small plate is 1
My large plate is not
The large plate is still 20
It's almost
About this
New
It's not new
This year's summary is complete
Then
Next is the third part
The third part
You can wait a little
Let Jamie heat the rice
Then we can rest for 5 minutes
You can chat for 5 minutes
I'm also in front of the camera
Because we didn't eat
I just want to say that everyone can be more relaxed
Eat and then
Talk to you while talking
Say some words
The fourth bag below
Is not worn
The fourth bag
Although it looks like it's worn
But in fact you can see
This fourth bag is actually
Outside
In fact, it should be inside
I just didn't put it in
Just go inside
It should be
Inside
But I put it outside
It seems to have been discovered by you
It's just far away
I didn't see it
Don't talk about feelings
Then
Let's talk about some plans for next year
Some plans for Malus Designer next year
Yes, it's going to start streaming
I have a new hat
My beloved green hat
Are you still watching
You can watch it on your internet
Please subscribe to my instagram
There will be a new video
I'm looking at that
In the chat
What can you see
What's my green hat
What kind of
In the chat
I also think that this green hat is very cute. The streamer chose Lin Ma's.
When Jin Mi is here, we can start the next part.
She went to heat up pizza, fried chicken, and barbecue.
Is this year going really fast?
How do you get into different models?
You just go in, file, file, and then...
Oh, I need some time to open the project file.
File, then go into OBJ.
After getting into OBJ, you can choose to be a model when you go in.
I also think that this green hat is very cute.
Can I be an MD model?
Yes, you can.
You can be an OBJ model.
What exactly are you doing?
Why do you have to secretly be an MD model?
Are you still in the company?
Yes, I'm still in the company.
Otherwise, how would you do a live stream?
Have you ever been an MD model?
Ah, just now, I was an MD model.
Are you referring to the Japanese style?
Japanese MD models are similar to Korean models.
It's quite simple.
You just match the inside of the Korean model with some white people.
Isn't that an MD model?
Study online.
But it's already late to study online now.
Because some of today's content has been added.
Fix the hat on the head.
For example, this is a corner.
Then you can use this.
Fix the hat to the virtual model.
Click on this.
Then click on the virtual model.
It will be fixed to the top.
Then it won't fall down again.
Oh, this won't scare me to death.
There's a bug.
Then just simulate it.
Is it Christmas?
Um...
It's not...
Yeah, there's no difference between folding pants and folding dresses.
Folding pants is actually...
For example, let's assume this is a pair of pants.
You stretch it horizontally.
Then draw some inner lines for it.
Then it can be folded.
Can you make clothes other than human?
Yes, you can.
Our promotional pictures are all made for dogs.
Christmas didn't work overtime.
Today's work time is in the afternoon.
So it's not overtime.
And it's also what we mentioned.
Actually...
Fortunately, Jin Mi is not here.
Actually, I wanted to say that Christmas is over.
That is, everyone is not here.
It's not that everyone is not here.
It's just that this period of time is empty.
Then...
Um...
This live broadcast...
I feel like...
It doesn't seem to have any summary of this year.
It's an old-fashioned...
Wow, it's like an old-fashioned feeling.
So I still want to say that I want to do a live broadcast.
Dogs are hard to wear.
This...
This is your version.
You have to change it a little bit.
Oh, my barbecue.
The barbecue is cold.
I don't know if it tastes good.
I don't know.
Oh, thank you.
He's heating up the barbecue again.
I'll take it out and eat it with shiitake mushrooms.
And then...
Uh...
It's about the new year.
Call Jin Mi over first.
Let him join in.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Jin Mi.
I don't know if I can see you.
Can you see me?
Everyone.
I want to appear next to you.
And then...
A new year.
Can you tell me what kind of activities there are in the new year?
Um...
The main activity is...
Uh...
This is also a...
A message from my friends who have stayed until now.
That is to say...
Uh...
Next year, Marvelous Designer will have an activity called Defeating Jin Mi every month.
And then...
This Defeating Jin Mi is because of this.
Jin Mi is a new member of our team.
And then...
He is also a college student who just graduated.
He just started to contact and use Marvelous Designer.
Although his current level has been...
Uh...
I've been learning for a while.
But...
We still hope to see you beat him.
Uh...
And then next year there will be...
There will be a competition every month.
It's called Defeating Jin Mi.
And then the content of this competition is...
Uh...
It's our unlimited topic.
It may be...
When the competition is on that day.
Just let the audience say a topic.
Uh...
You...
You go and do it for me.
What do you do?
Do a piece of cloth.
Do a cloth on the sofa.
Lean on a pillow.
Something like that.
And then in a certain time.
We will...
Uh...
Just randomly choose one.
Just randomly choose a little friend.
Maybe a B站 user.
Maybe a user of the Q group.
And then...
Of course, you can also sign up.
And then sign up for this game.
Have a battle with Jin Mi.
And then I will do a live broadcast.
And then at the end.
Everyone will vote.
Vote.
Who is the champion today?
And then...
For example, is it Jin Mi?
Or that person?
If it's Jin Mi.
He has no reward.
And then if it's...
And then if it's our...
Manless designer user.
You can draw a reward.
There will be red envelopes.
For example, 233.
666.
Is there 666?
I don't seem to know either.
Anyway, it's 233.
Anyway, there must be 233.
And then draw...
There must be 233.
I picked one inside a few red envelopes.
And then...
It's all about luck.
You'll be able to draw a lot of money.
And then in a few years,
it may be as good as 50 billing.
It may be as good as 50 billing.
And then...
In a few years,
I might have a bit under 50 cents.
Live直播不是.
promote live
It's just like a match.
And then...
This thing...
Every week...
Then it's not.
Because this thing...
Every week...
It's only available here.
So you sign up.
Every week...
We will...
We would really pick you.
Because all of us...
Everyone, especially the domestic fans, may be a little shy
So we still hope that everyone can participate in these events
So we held this event called Defeat the Secrets
Yes, money, money, isn't it?
When you hear money, everyone is very excited
And then every month there will be this money, we call it red envelope money
And then we haven't figured out if there will be a devil's challenge
The devil's challenge is to battle with me
Then if it's a devil, I think, if it's a devil's challenge
Will you give away the reward?
Not you, it's not you who pays, are you so happy?
I had previously said, I had previously said to them
That if Jin Mi loses, I will deduct your pocket money from Jin Mi's salary
This is deducting your red envelope money
I think this proposal will cause a lot of problems
Yes Yes Yes, I think this proposal will cause a lot of problems
It's also pretty good.
How much do you lose every month, how much do you deduct?
Yes, how much do you lose every month, how much do you deduct.
This is what is called
the iron fist of justice.
That is to say, the earlier you participate,
the easier it is to defeat me.
Yes, that's right. The earlier you participate,
the easier it is to defeat Jin Mi.
In January of next year,
you can sign up.
What is the MD course of the domestic system?
Because
although everyone
sees that I have been live streaming,
we still have some technical support.
But there are only two of us in MD.
Before Jin Mi came,
there was only me.
I was responsible for all the technical support,
training, making posters,
promotion, marketing, etc.
It's very lonely.
It's not lonely, it's tired.
There is no need to be lonely.
Whether you come or not is the same.
And then...
My little hand.
My little hand is near me.
This morning I also saw
a picture of a bat.
A bat said,
when I woke up one night,
all around me were my enemies.
So, in fact,
to do this MD course,
it's all
in a hurry.
It takes a few hours to do the course,
including preparing a live stream.
Our live stream is very short
and very fast, right?
But in fact,
there are a lot of things
to prepare and test
for the live stream.
Because every time I do a live stream,
I want to add some new things.
And then,
is there anything you haven't done before?
And is there anything I've never learned?
I may have to find out
how to make this dress myself.
There is.
There is our QQ group on the bottom left.
I don't know
if you don't usually use QQ.
But on WeChat,
I don't really like using WeChat.
I think WeChat is very troublesome.
And it's not convenient to share files.
WeChat also has a limit on the number of people.
The group can't be as large as 1,000 people.
Can you speak Chinese?
It's okay.
No, I don't speak Chinese.
I speak English.
Just send me a message.
And then,
other than defeating Jin Mi,
there are other activities.
Maybe next year,
there will be a clothing competition.
Only for Hana.
And then,
there is also a language group and a professional group.
It's almost the same as last year's Crytek.
And then,
there will still be a live stream every month.
maybe next year,
I will visit
some cities with more users
to have some exchanges.
And then,
yeah, that's it.
It's just a temporary plan.
Everyone knows that this plan
will never change.
At the beginning of this year,
we may think that
2020 is finally here.
No one would have thought that
the picture on Weibo
in 2020 would turn into an SOS balloon
and be printed in my head.
Hana's footstep.
Who discovered this?
Oh my god.
When did I open the model?
The clothes are more...
Oh,
it's okay to translate it into English.
We can do some translation in the future.
Yeah.
How does the foot recover?
The controller goes back.
Sorry.
Her foot fell off.
The professional group
has some
experience in 3D production.
They are some
more professional entrepreneurs.
The professional group.
The others are some
we will classify as the amateur group.
If you participate in
the competition,
they will let you fill in.
The rewards for these two
should be different.
I'm not sure about this.
It's just a plan.
I hope you can use
more MD in your daily life
and give some feedback.
Remember to add more groups.
These are the main things.
Then,
do you have any questions?
Any questions?
Because it's Christmas Eve today.
You may also
be busy.
It's our virtue
for everyone
to watch our live stream.
This model is
made by MD.
Look at my eyes.
It's made by MD.
If you want to ask
where this model is from,
this model is
built by our boss.
Today,
my calculation
can't be restored.
I have to redo it.
I haven't met this model before.
Have you tried MD-10?
I haven't encountered this problem
from the beginning to now.
How long is the live stream today?
It may be over by 10 o'clock.
There are still 5 minutes left.
Everyone is busy.
I have to go home soon.
I haven't eaten yet.
I have to eat the leftovers
in the office in a while.
How to sew the edge
between the two pieces of cloth?
You can sew it up.
Just take a piece of paper
and sew it on top.
I don't know if this is what I'm talking about.
The boss is Korean.
The skirt is at the bottom left.
There is a QQ skirt
and an inner line at the bottom left of the live stream.
Is the boss Korean?
Yes.
The boss is Korean.
My boss is
originally a 3D designer
and
I can't say if he is the boss.
He is the leader.
He was originally
a 3D designer
and later joined MD.
Does it help to modify the clothes?
No.
Because your fabric
is different.
If it's about the real
production and manufacturing of clothes,
you can go and look at
the other part of our company.
The software is called Cloth.
If the boss is a Chinese,
will the boss go to find a model?
Of course.
Our boss said
he wanted to give a panda to this live stream.
I don't know why.
Foreigners will always say
China is a panda.
Then he said
let me make a set of Santa's clothes for the panda.
I said do it.
Then my boss sent me a link.
Then he said
can you see this panda?
I said it's cute.
I looked at it and it was 149 dollars.
Then I said
this panda is so expensive.
Then my boss told me
don't think about whether this panda is expensive or not.
Then my boss said
I don't like pandas.
Actually it's not the boss.
It's another colleague.
He asked me if I want it.
I said I don't like pandas.
Then he said
don't think about the price.
I said I don't like pandas.
Then I looked at the 149 dollars.
I was thinking
why is it so expensive?
Then another colleague said
another colleague said
why is this panda so expensive?
I said let Jimmy lend you one.
Then he said
no need.
Do you have a photo?
No.
This is a normal panda.
It's even a bit like the panda in the panda show.
Do you understand?
I think it's similar to that panda.
I think the number of faces on the Internet is a little more.
It looks more detailed.
There is no kind of
picture on it.
It's just a very smooth panda.
I said 149 dollars.
Oh my god.
This is a real workaholic.
Which website is it on?
I don't know.
I also forgot.
Anyway, the boss sent me a website.
Because I don't search for these things.
Usually our boss buys it for us.
Yes.
I said
149 dollars.
I thought my eyes were crooked.
I thought it was 49 dollars.
I said
this panda.
I actually put a emoji on the panda's face.
I just asked.
Oh, the boss is.
Oh, it turned out to be like this.
No wonder.
Yes.
Now it's almost 10 o'clock.
If you have any questions, you can ask in the QQ group.
It's really late.
Thank you all for
giving me face today.
I'm willing to be on Christmas Eve.
I hope you all
in the future,
have a good time.
It's 2021 soon.
You can all
cheer up.
Don't work overtime.
Because the heaven didn't work overtime.
Christmas is a good time.
I mainly want to introduce Jimmy to everyone
because he is a new colleague of the company.
Then everyone will have some questions in the community.
You can add me or add him.
I hope everyone will add me more.
Then it's good.
I hope everyone will add him more.
then don't ask me
Of course I'm just kidding, I'm not telling the truth
I'm afraid that some people will think that I'm telling the truth
but that's not the case
Yes, everyone, happy Christmas, okay?
That's it for today
Eh, my screen is black
Everyone, oh, I finally know
Because I, because I found out that my screen was black before
I'll go and press the control key
As a result, I press the control key to open the screen
Okay, that's it for today
Everyone, goodbye, bye bye
Bye bye
Bye bye, everyone, goodbye, bye bye
Happy Christmas, bye bye
Bye bye, bye bye